http://www.tax-tiger.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Effective and updated on August, 2014:Your Privacy is of the utmost concern to Tax Tiger, first and foremost! This privacy statement explains how we collect and use the information which you submit to Tax Tiger.We understand that you share private and sensitive information in order to help us evaluate and resolve your tax problems. We want you to feel comfortable in sharing that information, knowing that we will hold that information which you have entrusted to our firm to the highest privacy standards. Rest assured, we will protect your privacy and under no circumstances, will Tax Tiger sell or share any of the personal information collected on this website, during your consultation, or throughout the process of your case, with any person or organization except as authorized by you. We will use the specific information collected on this website (Name, Address, Email, Phone Number, etc), to respond to your request regarding the reason you contacted us, as well as to provide tax related information and/or any future offers of service.If you are only a visitor to the web site, we do not collect personal information unless you specifically provide it to us through the submission of our contact web form, or through calling us directly. www.Tax-Tiger.com may use “cookies”, a technology which allows us to track the traffic patterns of individuals as they browse our web site for informational and research purposes only.If you have provided or submitted information to us, and would like for your information to be accessed, updated, or removed from our database, or to opt out of any further marketing or information related communications at any time, you may do this by contacting us at privacy@taxtiger.comFrom time to time we may update the information contained in this privacy policy at any time. In the event we update our privacy policy, we will notify you through the email address we have on file. In the event you did not provide an email address to us, we would encourage you to check back periodically for updated information.You may also contact us regarding our privacy policy by writing us at the address below:Tax Tiger
6355 Riverside Blvd, Suite L
Sacramento, CA 95831
Email: privacy@taxtiger.com
Phone: 866-667-3829
We service the entire United States from locations in Denver, Colorado; Minneapolis & St Paul, Minnesota; the San Francisco Bay Area, San Diego & Orange County, & Sacramento, California. To find out more, get in touch by visiting our contact page and filling out the form.Privacy Policy |Disclaimer Copyright 2020
Tax Tiger
.
Designed by
White Hat
